pricepanda.com.ph 2014-10-06

# Privacy Policy | visit PricePanda Philippines

PRICEPANDA.COM.PH ("SITE") IS CREATED AND REGISTERED UNDER Pricepanda Group GmbH. WE SUGGEST EVERYONE TO READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY. BY ACCESSING THE SITE AND USING THE WEB AND MOBILE SERVICES PROVIDED BY PRICEPANDA.COM.PH ("SERVICE"), YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS DESCRIBED HERE, INCLUDING ANY FUTURE MODIFICATIONS TO THESE TERMS OF SERVICES AND GUIDELINES. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ANY OF THE AGREEMENTS STATED HERE, PLEASE CEASE USING THE SERVICE IMMEDIATELY. 

##  1\. Our Commitment To Privacy 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. We may change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy policy in the “Privacy Policy” section of the website. 

##  2\. Types of Information Collected and Uses of Collected Information 

We collect two types of information about our Website Users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information.  
 **Personally Identifiable Information**. Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies a specific End User. When you engage in certain activities on the Website, such as creating an account, filling out a survey, ordering a product or service from us, posting a review, sending us feedback, requesting information about our services, or applying for a job through the Website (collectively, "Identification Activities"), we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself. It is optional for you to engage in an Identification Activity. If you elect to engage in an Identification Activity, however, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information about yourself, such as your first and last name, mailing address, email address, telephone number and date of birth. Depending on the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some is identified as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information for a particular activity that requires it, you will not be permitted to engage in that activity. We use Personally Identifiable Information to provide products and services to you, enhance the operation of the Website, administer contests, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, analyze Website use, improve our product and service offerings, and to tailor your experience with third parties as provided in Item 3 of this Privacy Policy. For example, if you send our customer service an email we may use your comments and feedback to tell others about our services, and may post your comment in our marketing materials or on our Website. In addition, if you use our Website to send information or a product to another person, we may store your personal information, and the personal information of any recipient. We may use that other person’s contact information to allow him or her to view and accept your gift or to allow the recipient to access the information you requested we send. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, resolve disputes, accomplish administrative tasks, contact you, enforce our agreements with you, including our Website Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. **Non-Personally Identifiable Information**. Non-Personally Identifiable Information is information that does not identify a specific End User. This type of information may include things like the Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") of the website you visited before coming to our Website, the URL of the website you visit after leaving our Website, the type of browser you are using and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. We, and/or our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers, may automatically collect this information when you visit our Website through the use of electronic tools like Cookies and Web beacons or Pixel tags, as described in Items 4 and 8 of this Privacy Policy.

We use Non-Personally Identifiable Information to troubleshoot, administer the Website, analyze trends, gather demographic information, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. We may also share this information with our authorized Third Party Service Providers and Advertisers to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, and programming. 

##  3\. Release of Personally Identifiable Information 

We will not share your Personally Identifiable Information with other parties except as provided below:  
 **We may share your information with PricePanda Merchants**. From time to time, we provide offers from particular merchants (referred to as “PricePanda Merchants”) who, as part of the offer, request information on PricePanda customers who were redirected to the merchant’s website/store. In those cases, we share some of your Personally Identifiable Information with PricePanda Merchants. Sharing this Information will allow a PricePanda Merchant to market directly to you should they choose to do so. However, we will only share Personally Identifiable Information with a PicePanda Merchant if you engage in an Identification Activity, and then only to the PricePanda Merchant involved in that Identification Activity. Please note that we will only provide a PricePanda Merchant your information with an opt-in notice to you, in which you will have a chance to choose that PricePanda not give the PricePanda Merchant your personal information. We specifically disclaim any responsibility or liability for the actions of such PricePanda Merchant. While we inform them that they are only permitted to communicate with you for the purposes of the specific promotion with PricePanda, we do not have any responsibility for the actions of the PricePanda Merchant, and the actions of the PricePanda Merchant are not in our control. **We may share your information with Authorized Third Party Service Providers**. We provide some of our services and products through third parties. These "Third Party Service Providers" perform functions on our behalf, like sending out and distributing our administrative and promotional emails. We may share your Personally Identifiable Information with such Service Providers to send postal or email, remove repetitive information on customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, operate the Website, troubleshoot, and provide customer service. We may also collect personal information from individuals and companies ("Affiliates") with whom we have business relationships and may have to also share their information with Service Providers to accomplish our administrative tasks. We encourage Third Party Service Providers to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by such parties is governed by the privacy policies of such parties and is not subject to our control.

 **We may share your information in a Business Transfer**. As with any other business, we could merge with, or be acquired by another company. If this occurs, the successor company would acquire the information we maintain, including Personally Identifiable Information. However, Personally Identifiable Information would remain subject to this Privacy Policy. **We may share your information for our Protection and the Protection of Others**. We may also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law or a court order; enforce or apply this Privacy Policy, our Website Terms of Use or other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of the Website, its Users or others. 

##  4\. Release of Non-Personally Identifiable Information 

We may disclose or share Non-Personally Identifiable Information with Partners, Affiliates and Advertisers. For example, we may share aggregated demographic information (which does not include any Personally Identifiable Information) with "Third Party Advertisers" or "Third Party Advertising Companies" and other parties as provided below:

We use Third Party Advertising Companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide, through the use of network tags, advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

We also use Third Party Service Providers to track and analyze Non-Personally Identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our Users to administer our Website and constantly improve its quality. We may also publish this information for promotional purposes or as a representative audience for Advertisers. Please note that this is not Personally Identifiable Information, only general summaries of the activities of our Users. Such data is collected on our behalf, and is owned and used by us. 

##  5\. Updating and Correcting Information 

We believe that you should have the ability to access and edit the Personally Identifiable Information you provide us. You may change any of your Personally Identifiable Information by sending us an email at support@pricepanda.com. Please indicate your name and email address, and what information you would like to update when you contact us. We encourage you to promptly update your Personally Identifiable Information if it changes. In addition, in may be impossible for us to completely delete all of your information because we periodically backup information. 

##  6\. Security of Information 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies which do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Website, and are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information. 

##  7\. Data Tracking 

**Cookies**. To facilitate and customize your experience with the Website, we store cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a User's computer for record-keeping purposes which contains information about that User. We use cookies to save you time while using the Website, remind us who you are, and track and target User interests in order to provide a customized experience. Cookies also allow us to collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information from you, like which pages you visited and what links you clicked on. Use of this information helps us to create a more user-friendly experience for all visitors. In addition, we may use Third Party Advertising Companies to display advertisements on our Website. As part of their service, they may place separate cookies on your computer. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by our Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any Advertiser. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able to modify your browser settings to decline cookies. Please note that if you decline or delete these cookies, some parts of the Website may not work properly.

 **Other Tracking Devices**. We may use other industry standard technologies like pixel tags and web beacons to track your use of our Website pages and promotions, or we may allow our Third Party Service Providers to use these devices on our behalf. Pixel tags and web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on certain pages on our Website, or in our emails that allow us to determine whether you have performed a specific action. When you access these pages or open or click an email, pixel tags and web beacons generate a Non-Personally Identifiable notice of that action. Pixel tags allow us to measure and improve our understanding of visitor traffic and behavior on our Website, as well as give us a way to measure our promotions and performance. We may also utilize pixel tags and web beacons provided by our Affiliates and/or Marketing Partners for the same purposes. 

##  8\. Privacy Policies of Third Party Websites 

This Privacy Policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. Other websites that may be accessible through this Website have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. If you link to any such website, we urge you to review the website's privacy policy. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties.
